Guide to the Floyd R. Newman papers, 1893-1990.
Newman, Floyd R. papers, 1893-1990
- Cornell University
  - Christine Snow (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Applications to Cornell (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Michael J. Browne, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Doug Savoca (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Catherine McFadden (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Susan Holcombe (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Polly Whitmore (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Kenneth Jones (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Thomas R. Briggs, Professorship of Engineering, June 22, 1964 - July 11, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - FRN military collection (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Club of Northeastern Ohio luncheon, Union Club, Cleveland, Oct. 31, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Mark Finklestein (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - William H. Marsh (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Applications to Cornell, 1965: William A. Kuchler, Barneveld, NY, Ag. - accepted; Susan J. Hainge, Houston, Texas, Arts Sciences - accepted; Kenneth Geluso, Oyster Bay, NY, Vet. - rejected (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Applications, 1966: Linda Whitmore, Plandome, NY, College of Home Economics - rejected; Gary M. Kaye, Forest Hills, NY, Arts Sciences - accepted (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Applications, 1967: Roy Glenn Ellington, Portland, Oregon (no application submitted) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Applications, 1968: Neil C. Frazee, Maitland, Florida (rejected) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Applications, 1971: John D. Lynn III, Huntington, NY (School of Hotel Administration), rejected; Lawrence Harrison Wilson, Rydal, Penn. (College of Arts Sciences), accepted (Mrs. Larry E. Gubb) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Applications, 1963: Willet F. Whitmore, Jr. accepted by C.U. (but did not enter); Ruth Foster, accepted, National Merit Scholarship; Gail Ready, accepted (Arts Sciences) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Applications, 1964: Candace L. Smith, Lake Oswego, Oregon; Glenn Jones, Medina, Ohio (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Applications, 1970 -1971: Anne Kitchen (Otto Wanek, Jr.), entrance application not made (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Applications, 1971 -1972: Robert Terry Modney (Law), rejected; John F. Dunning (Eng.), accepted; Patrick Nakao (Arts), accepted (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Applications, 1973: Lisa Christine Crofts, put on "wait list" and withdrew her application; John Meredith Miller III, rejected; Frederick R. Ormsby, rejected (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Applications, 1973 -1974: Susan Douglass, Shaker Heights, Ohio (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Applications, 1976: Mark E. Swanson, Virginia Beach, Virginia; Hal Mark Kahn, Medina, Ohio (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Applications, 1974: Elaine Mead, Makati, Rizal, Philippines, accepted (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Applications (prospective and tentative), 1950 -1952: Accepted - David Browning Mann, Robert Graves, Tom Merry weather, Win. Alexander Patterson, David P. Smith; rejected - Paul E. VanHorn, Jr., Gordon Peter Bonfante, John Lee Forker, James L. Longacre, Win. D. Tway (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1912 Memorial, 1061-82 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Transcript - Cornell Fund Dinner, Cleveland, Feb. 22, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - James A. Weeks Professorship (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ithaca Journal supplement re Cayuga Lake, May 13, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Membership rosters, Cornell U. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 16, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - IRA champions, June 18, 1955 (John M. VanHorn) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - IRA, June 19, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - C.U. Varsity Crew, Henley, England, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Varsity Crew, 1957; IRA Syracuse, NY, June 22, 1957; Henley, England, July 5-6, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 17, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 16, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 15, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 19-20, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 19, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 18, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 17, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 14, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, June 19, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - IRA Regatta, Lake Onondaga, Finals, June 3, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Family party, Syracuse, NY, June 2-4, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cornell 57 - Columbia 20, Baker Field, NYC, Oct. 31, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - CU 3 - Harvard 3, Ithaca, Oct. 16, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cornell 16 - Yale 14, Ithaca, Oct. 22, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cornell 47 - Princeton 13, Ithaca, Oct. 14, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Harvard 14 - Cornell 12, Ithaca, Oct. 21, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cornell 41 - Harvard 24, Ithaca, Oct. 18, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame 12th Annual Awards Dinner (Pres. Nixon), NYC, Dec. 9, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cornell - U. of Penn., Ithaca, Oct. 10, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cornell football (Ed. Marinaro), 1971, tie, Ivy League Title (Dartmouth) (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Football, general, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Football, 1974 - Michigan State 16, OSU 13 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - C.U. various - football, crew, hockey, etc. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Miscellany
  - THE WEEK THAT WAS! Hot Springs, Virginia (The Homestead), Nov. 27-29, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Roanoke, Virginia, Nov. 30-Dec. 1, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Crystal City Marriott, Washington, Dec. 2-3, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - The history-making snowfall, Medina-Akron, Ohio - 20"-22"-24", Nov. 30-Dec. 1, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Charitable gifts - various (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Circular letters, 1973 -1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Photo mailing - FRN and HAN, May 21, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - FRN personal possessions - disposition, 1976 -1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - FRN personal data, 1951 -1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Road directions to FRN residence etc., 1953 -1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Daily office record, Nov. 29, 1982 - Apr. 10, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - FRN correspondence lists, 1975 -1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Calendars made for FRN's ease of reading (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Insurance - Hemlock Hollow/Little L Farm - appraisal, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - FRN 90th birthday party, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Letter of credit, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - FRN notes re various stories (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "Kiplinger Washington Letter" (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - "Platt's Oilgram News" (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Photo mailings re FRN Log Cabin, etc. (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - FRN auto accident, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Apples - list of varieties (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Telephone lists (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Address lists (Box 10, Folder 35-36)
  - Photo mailing - FRN age 3 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - World War I Experiences - "Allied Oil Private" (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Original Sacher Torte - Hotel Sacher, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - National Cyclopedia of American Biography (James T. White Co.) (Robert J. Steele), 1971 -1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Membership roster - petroleum industry (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Membership rosters - clubs (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - FRN remarks (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Japanese story (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - FRN notes, 1987 -1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Genesee Country Village, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Maple syrup lists, 1983 -1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Maple syrup lists, 1979 -1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Maple syrup lists, 1951 -1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Phyliss Streidl (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Phyliss Streidl story (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Jonathan Streidl, Plainville, Michigan, The Armington Award, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - FRN absences from 862 H.H. - (Dates) - and some travel expenses, Jan. 1952 -1972 (Box 11, Folder 13-17)
  - Etching, 26 Broadway, NYC Socony Training Class 1912, NY Sun Apr. 13, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Shanghai story (Box 11, Folder 19-21)
  - A.M. mailing list - Shanghai, 1912 -1916 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - C.U. Testimonial Dinner, FRN, Hollenden Hotel, Cleveland, Apr. 14, 1970 - preliminary arrangements (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - C.U. Testimonial Dinner, FRN, Hollenden Hotel, Cleveland, Apr. 14, 1970 - lists and invitations (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - C.U. Testimonial Dinner - letters, follow-ups (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - C.U. Testimonial Dinner - letters, cont'd; various -R.S. Blazer, John L. Collyer; remarks - FRN, R.S. Blazer (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - C.U. Testimonial Dinner - newsclippings, misc. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Testimonial Dinner, Cleveland, Feb. 22, 1949 - master file -copy of everything mailed to Dr. Gould, Cornell University Archivist (Box 11, Folder 28-32)
  - Testimonial Dinner, Feb. 22, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
- Allied Oil Company, Inc.
  - J.A. Weeks - Allied Oil, FRN B-Day (80) Party, Nov. 23, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - James A. Week and Gould P. Colman visit with FRN (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 90th B-Day Party - FRN's "Good Luck Story" (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Survey Water Transportation, 1926 -1928 (from NYC to Cleveland), A.T. Banning, Jr., T.S. Killion (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Parade Studios, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Photo Schaja, 1969 -1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Photo Schaja, 1956 -1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Photo Schaja, 1959 - (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Aesthetic Illumination - H.H. (John Watson), Sept. 1961 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - List of donees (Allied Oil Co.) - 1948 (Sard binoculars); list of donees - personal photos, 1948 -1949 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc. and subsidiary companies: summary of operations, 1939 - 1943 (Aug. 28, 1943) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc. (its subsidiaries and associated companies) (July 10, 1941 ) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc.: operations - physical facilities (to A. Clarke, Bedford, S.O. Co., New Jersey - 1943 ) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - M.R. Wiseman (E.D. Retter), gasoline et cetera sales -Canton Refining Co., March-April, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - SOCONY training school at 26 Broadway (NY Sun Apr. 13, 1913 ) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - FRN biographic information, Jar. 1, 1952 - published articles (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc. - Harvard Grad School of Business Administration (Taxation 30 - 1954 ) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Statement of W.W. Vanderveer (Nov. 3, 1949 ) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Crude Oil Terminal - Toledo, 1940 -1948 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Allied Wholesale Foods Division, 1946 -1947 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Personal letters from business and personal friends on the occasion of the allied-Ashland merger effective Aug. 2, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc. - confidential memos (Box 12, Folder 21-25)
  - "Allied Private" (story of gas and oil - World War I) (Box 12, Folder 26-28)
  - Allied Oil Co. Inc. - its subsidiaries and associated companies (July 10, 1941 ) (Box 12, Folder 29-31)
  - Commercial value, May 31, 1945 (Ford, Bacon Davis) (Box 12, Folder 29-31)
  - Merger - Allied and Ashland ( 1948 ) (Box 12, Folder 29-31)
  - Data - history of Allied - Otto Scott, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 29-31)
  - Allied Oil, Inc. - lease, debenture notes, etc. 1925 -1944 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc. (Central Pi L. Co. and Cleveland tankers) - copies of letters and memos, 1948, memos, letter, 1939, 1948, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Allied Oil Co., Inc. - Twentieth Anniversary letters, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Shipping records (tank cars), 1925 -1926 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Sales records (tank cars) (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Confidential files, Arthur E. Dietz Co., 1938 -1948 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Confidential files, A. P. Byal, 1933 -1942 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Confidential files, A.R. Patterson, 1936 -1945 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Confidential files, Charles W. Scott (James A. Weeks) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Confidential files, Charles W. Scott (FRN) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Confidential files, W.E. Weidler, 1937 -1946 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Confidential files, Charles L. Wedell, 1937 -1947 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Confidential files, H. Merritt Woodward (Perry A. Peterson) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Vols.1-2: Ashland Oil Refining Co. preferred stock, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
  - Vol.: Ashland Oil Refining Co. merger, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Report Commercial Value Allied Oil Co., Inc. and subsidiaries as of Jan. 1, 1945, May 31, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Golden Anniversary The Oil and Gas Journal, May 1951 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - "World Oil," Dec. 1949 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Vol.: International Petroleum Register 1950 Storage Tank Fittings 28th edition (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Vol.: International Petroleum Register 1966 -1967 38th edition (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Personal business notes (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, snapshots, etc. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Fuel oil circulars, etc., 1920 -1927 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Rexford S. Blazer - Profit Sharing Plan, 1941 -1958 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Addresses (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Allied baseball records, 1934 -1942, Harbor View, Regnatz, Inc. - "Newman's Notables," "Vandeveer's Vanquished Veterans" (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - Christmas lists, 1936 -1947 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Bonds purchased from Merrill, Turben Co.; Hayden, Miller Co; Hornblower Weeks (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - "The Lamp" (75th anniversary of Jersey Standard), June 1957 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Allied Oil blotters (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Charles C. Scott (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Rexford S. Blazer (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Canadian correspondence, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - FRN history - Allied Oil - stories (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Ben Smart, 1949 -1950 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Preferred Stock, 1948 -1951 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - FRN notes, J.A. Weeks history (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Sales 1-15, Common Stock, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 18-21)
  - American Petroleum Products Co., Fuel Oil Sales Reports, etc., 1920 -1924 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Fuel Oil Sales Reports, 1920 -1923 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous reports up to 1920 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Reports, etc. - details, purchases, 1920 -1924 (Box 29, Folder 25-26)
  - Reports, miscellany (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Pipe line maps - oil and gas production maps, 1940 -1950 (Box 29, Folder 28-32)
- Family, Relatives
  - Dorothy Barben (Mrs. Fred W.) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Henrietta Bame/Peter H. Bame, 1965 -1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - David C. and Mildred Duncan, 1963 -1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - David C. and Cris Duncan, 1981 -1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Gordon and Jane Duncan, 1980 -1991 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - James W. and Bevan Duncan (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Janet H. Duncan, 1985 -1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Robert N. Marian Peck (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ruby A. Newman (locked file), 1943 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - John M. Van Horn, 1966 -1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ruth and David Van Horn, 1981 -1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - John M. Van Horn, 1962 -1967 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - John M. Van Horn (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Jeannette M. Zwetsch (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - J.C. and Hattie Newman - 25th wedding anniversary (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Beth Salisbury (Mrs. Malcolm L. ) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Peck and Company, Inc. (Bradley's Pine Hills AW), 1965 -1973 (Robert N. Peck) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Mrs. Ward (Ada) Cummings Mrs. Roy N. Cummings Mrs. Carrie M. Phelps (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - John A. Newman ' s Pioneer Village, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Family party (FRN - 80th b-day), Nov. 25, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - "Recollections" (and Reminiscences) by David C. Duncan (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - "Recollections" comments, FRN Exchanged letters By S. Alden Perrine (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Marie M. Newman - Thompson, Hine and Flory H.H. Atkinson, 1944 -1945 and Paul Lamb, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Marie Newman, 1940 -1945 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Paul and Monika Maslowski (Trust 430140) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Marie Newman (Trust 435270) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Irrevocable Trust Agreement, Oct. 31, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sophia Ramsdell Trust - settlement of estate (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mary Webb - Clara Lapp, 1946 -1956 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - NYC - Atlantic City - Philadelphia (HAN - FRN), 1949 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Letters etc. to "Queen Mary," various et cetera (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Lois Schmidt - Ithaca visit, June 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ithaca, State College - Lois Schmidt - Rochester (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Lois P. Schmidt (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Family recipes - favorite sayings, etc. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Ruth Newman Van Horn Foundation, 1955 -1964 (Box 15, Folder 15-17)
- Churchville
  - Reception, Old Friends Reunion and buffet, Johnson House, Churchville. July 29, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Reception, Old Friends Reunion, Sept. 21, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Churchville, 1984 -1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - New Municipal Building (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Newman-Riga Library, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
  - Free Riga Library (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Janet Rabin (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Church affairs (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Churchville, NY Union Congregational United Church of Christ (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Burton Sage (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Churchville Lodge #667 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Miscellany (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Monroe County, NY YMCA (Win. F. Brunk) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Robert C. Stewart, Rochester - conveyance of vacant lot 30 S. Main St. to Town of Riga, 1958 -1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Riga Free Library - correspondence - Free Enterprisers, 1948 -1951 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Riga Free Library - legal correspondence, dedication Oct. 17, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Purchase of Claude Property - search, deeds, etc., 1944 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Acquisition of park - and gift to Village of Churchville (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Travel
  - Japan, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Brussels, Paris, Luxembourg, Dusseldorf, etc., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Japan and Hong Kong (and San Francisco, Hawaii and Seattle) (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
  - 'Round the World, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
  - Japan, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Beirut and vicinity, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Teheran (Iran) and vicinity, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Bangkok (Thailand) (also Cambodia), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Singapore, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Istanbul (Turkey), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 'Round the World, 1969, 1962 - India etc. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 'Round the World, Hong Kong (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 'Round the World, Rangoon (Burma), 1959, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Japan and Tokyo, etc. (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
  - Italy, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 25-26)
  - Central Germany and Black Forest, 1956 -1960 (Box 17, Folder 2-Jan)
  - South Germany and Bavaria, 1956 -1960 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Ohio - motor trips - places to visit (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - State College, Quakertown, Reston, W. Virginia, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New England and East New York State, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Houston, Coleman, Raywood, New Orleans, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Cincinnati, Lexington, Berea, Ky, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - California, Hawaii, Portland, Ore., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
  - Florida - East coast, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Florida - D.M. Ward - circulars and various (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Florida - West coast (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Florida - East coast (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Florida - Tampa, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Florida, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Florida - maps, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Florida - East coast, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Florida - West coast, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 19-21)
  - Rye Town Hilton Inn - wedding, Adrienne Targus Kirkpatrick, Greenwich, Conn., Sept. 6, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Denver, Sept. 1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Oklahoma, Arkansas, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - New England, 1965 -1966, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - California maps (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Northwest Canada, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "The Great Northwest," Dec. 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Motor trip to West Coast, Apr. 4, 1960 (see "Note Book" for detailed info) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Seattle - Northwest (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Portugal, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Japan, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Texas, New Orleans, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
  - U.S. maps, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Various (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Texas, Oklahoma and Monterrey, Mexico, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Webbers - Japan, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Mr. Shiro Endo - Kobe, Japan - correspondence, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - BOAC (Hotels) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - NYC - 'Round the World, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - KLM, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - NYC - Amsterdam, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - 'Round the World, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - North and East (outside NYC) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New York City (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia - Washington - South (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Ohio - Kentucky - Middle East (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Chicago - Middle West (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - U.S. - general (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Texas - Oklahoma - South West (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - New Orleans (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Arizona - New Mexico (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - California (outside San Francisco) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - San Francisco (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Reno - Far West (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - National Geographic - India, Japan, China, 1921 -1923 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Brussels, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Maps, 1962; RTW 1963 (Box 19, Folder 15-17)
  - Switzerland - Feb. 1961 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - Turkey, Lebanon, Jordan, Iran (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Morocco, 1963 -1965 (Box 19, Folder 21-22)
  - Newspapers - Cairo, Jan. 1963 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Iran (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - India, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Taiwan, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Thailand - Cambodia - Singapore - Burma (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Egypt, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - India - Near East - Egypt, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Paris and Western Europe (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Japan - correspondence, 1955 -1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Japan - general (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Turkey - Iran, Lebanon, Egypt - Near East - Greece (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Thailand, Philippines, SE Asia (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Hong Kong - correspondence, 1955 -1965 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Africa (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "The Orient" (The Far East) - general (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - India, Nepal, Bhutan, Sikkin, Burma (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Purchase invoices, 1955, Japan - Hong Kong; 1959, Japan- Hong Kong (and Bangkok) (also, U.S. Customs file Apr. 26, 1959 ) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hong Kong, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Japan, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Shanghai, China etc., magazine articles (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Highlights and general travel suggestions (as of Apr. 1953 ) (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Italy (and Sicily), France (Riviera), Switzerland, Germany, France (Paris), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 21-23)
  - Nevada and vicinity, 1944 -1945 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Mexico, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Mexico, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Mexico, Nov.-Dec. 1961 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Highlights and general travel suggestions (as of Apr. 1953 ) Italy, Venice, Florence (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Highlights in France (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - France, Feb. 1961 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - France - outside of paris (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - General travel suggestions - Europe, particularly France and Paris (as of Feb. 1953 ) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Europe, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
  - Memos - France, Switzerland, Germany, 1948 -1949, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - North and Northwest Germany, 1952 -1958 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Germany, 1949 -1952 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Germany - general, 1958 -1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.R. Quill, Reno, Nev., visit to NY (sightseeing suggestions), 1960; also, Mr. and Mrs. H. Justus Neuman, May 18, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Larry E. Gubb - Round-the-World, 1960 itinerary; France, 1951, Russia, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
  - Various travel suggestions - Mrs. Maxine Sarstedt (Union Club) Hong Kong, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)